# **CEKDAR CAPAR**

Address: Hancioğlu street NO:99 Maltepe / ISTANBUL

Phone: +90 531 258 04 88

Email: cekdarcapar@gmail.com

Birth Date: 23.02.1998, Mersin

#### **SUMMARY**

After graduating from university, I started my work life and worked as an intern at the Customs Consultancy office for a short period. I started learning Adobe Premiere Pro and changed my field of work and decided to become a Social Media Specialist. I became interested in software while working at social media, and received a lot of training on it. At first, I received game development training with Unity and 7 months later published my first game on Google Play. To receive professional training, I attended Software Specialist training (250 hours) from Arı Bilgi Educational Institution. This training laid a good foundation for me and I am currently developing many projects for my own development.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Freelancer Social Media Specialist

May 2019- June 2022

- Communicated with other departments and created a unique and effective digital marketing strategy
- Created engaging and captivating content for an organisation's social media sites such as blogs, articles, posts and multimedia content

### **Intern-Ercan Customs Consultancy**

June 2018 - September 2018

• During internship as a customs consultant, gained significant experience in customs procedures, document preparation, customs declarations, and customer relations.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor Degree**

September 2019 - Present

University of Anadolu

· Major in Business Managment.

#### **Associate Degree**

September 2016 - June 2018

University of Dumlupinar

Major in Foreign Trade

#### **PROJECTS**

Meeting Room Reservation - https://github.com/cekdarcpr/Reservation\_Proje01

Developed a comprehensive reservation system for meeting rooms using ASP.NET. The system included several key features:

- **API Integration:** Integrated APIs to streamline data exchange and communication between different modules of the system.
- Dashboard: Implemented a user-friendly dashboard interface for easy navigation and management of reservations.
- Admin Panel: Created an admin panel with advanced functionalities such as user management, room allocation, and reporting.
- **Reservation Functionality:** Developed the core functionality for users to book meeting rooms, manage bookings, and receive notifications.

#### **VOLUNTEER HIGHLIGTS**

#### Volunteer, Istanbul KIZILAY

• Volunteered to work for blood donation encouragement. Informed people that came for blood donation. Helped them with providing the information for filling out the forms for donation.

## Volunteer, Istanbul TEKNOFEST

• Teknofest is a technology fair which is held by the Ministry of Industry in the former airport of Istanbul(Ataturk Airport). As a field staff, directed to the people for introducing the fair, take a walk to show the atmosphere of technology and encouraged the people in order to involve them in competitions. Has developed herself in teamwork and recognized the importance of being a volunteer for society.

### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

- Technical Skills: Microsoft SQL Server, C#, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Asp.Net, Asp.Net MVC, Web Services API, React, React Native, Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe Photoshop
- Languages: Turkish Native , English Beginner
- **Certifications:** Software Speacialist(C#), Java Developer(Udemy), React and React Native Developer(BT Academy).